zimbra.com 2019-11-04

# Privacy Policy

**Effective June 18, 2019**

Synacor, Inc. (“Synacor”) is a global technology company providing Internet solutions to enable clients, media companies and advertisers to build close relationships with consumers on the Internet. We provide and manage websites, and provide hosted email, mobile applications, and other services to and for parties that we enter into written agreements with (“Clients”), as well as provide advertising on our Clients’ websites, in email, mobile applications and to third parties for their websites (collectively, the “Services”). Synacor works to ensure that the Personal Data (as defined below) of its end users, including its Clients’ end users, will be kept safe and confidential.

In addition, Synacor owns and operates the following websites: [www.synacor.com](https://www.synacor.com/), www.synacor.net and [www.zimbra.com](https://www.zimbra.com/) (“Synacor Websites”).

This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect, how we collect it, why we collect it, and how you can request that we update, manage, export and delete your information. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Data” shall mean any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect process and/or use through our Services and the Synacor Websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that we legitimately collect through other channels, such as information that we collect offline, or from other websites.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacypolicy@synacor.com](mailto:privacypolicy@synacor.com).

### Introduction

Synacor uses the information collected by and provided to us in order to provide the Services and to improve the quality of the Services, to provide you with customized content according to your preferences, and to provide aggregate reporting, including disclosing some aggregate information and user statistics to current and prospective clients, advertisers, and content partners in order to describe our Services. The information that we collect depends on how you use our Services and how you manage your privacy controls on your device. Because our offerings and features may change from time to time, the options you have to provide us with Personal Data may change.

### Information You Provide to Us

When you create an account with one of our Clients, you provide us with Personal Data that includes your name and a password. You might also provide your phone number or your email address to receive updates or information about our Services or those of our Clients or to be contacted in connection with a job opening at Synacor.

We collect Personal Data (for example, your login credentials or password) via the Client Websites when you choose to provide it to us and/or when we received it from our Clients. In addition, you or our Client may provide demographic information (such as zip code or age), or other information as part of registration, sign-in, completing surveys, requests for product information or otherwise. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of the special features of the Client Websites. Please note that we do not control the data collected via the Client Websites, we only act as a data processor of this data on behalf of our Clients. As a data processor, we will not share, sell, rent, or trade with third parties for their marketing purposes any Personal Data collected by us, unless you give us consent to do so.

We also collect Personal Data that you provide to us via the Synacor Websites. In this situation, we are the data controller. Some examples of situations where you might provide Personal Data to us include:

  * Creating an account
  * Signing up for email alerts and newsletters
  * Completing a form related to one of our products or Services
  * Uploading a resume and applying for a job
  * Contacting us for technical support or customer service

If you choose to correspond with Synacor through e-mail, Synacor may retain the content of the correspondences, the e-mail addresses and our responses. You may sign-up to receive marketing emails or other communications from us. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may update your email preferences by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you.

Synacor may work with third party service providers to augment some of the information you provide on the Synacor and Client Websites. For example, if you have provided your email address via the Synacor and Client Websites, we may work with a third party data company to determine your age and zip code, and add that information to our database to create more tailored advertising, content and products.

We also store the content you create, upload or receive from others when using our Services. This includes things like the emails you write and receive if you are using our email service and comments you make on blogs. In addition, if any of our Services include user-generated content, we will collect any Personal Data contained therein.

### Information We Collect as You Use our Services

#### **Apps, Browsers & Devices**

When you download and use our Services through our mobile applications, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier.

We send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information.

#### **Your Activity**

We collect information about your activity in our Services, which we use to enhance your experience when using our Services. This activity information may include:

  * Terms you use when conducting an online search
  * Videos you watch
  * Views and interactions with content and ads
  * Voice and audio information when you use audio features
  * Purchase activity
  * People with whom you communicate via email or share content
  * Activity on third-party sites and apps that use our Services

You can contact us at [privacypolicy@synacor.com](mailto:privacypolicy@synacor.com) to find and manage activity information that we collect from you.

#### **Your Location Information**

We collect information about your location when you use our Services, which we use to enhance your experience when using our Services. Your location can be determined with varying degrees of accuracy by:

  * Browser or device-provided location information
  * IP address
  * Information about things near your device, such as Wi-Fi access points, cell towers and Blue-tooth enabled devices
  * Zip Code

The types of location data we collect depends in part on your device and account settings. For example, you can turn your Android device’s location on or off using the device’s settings app. You can also turn on location history if you want to save and manage your location information.

#### **Information Collected Automatically**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, domain type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, and to enhance our marketing, analytics, and site functionality. IP addresses are also used to provide us an audit trail in the case of any attempted illegal or unauthorized use of the Synacor and Client Websites or mobile applications.

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile applications on your device. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any Personal Data you submit within the mobile applications.

#### **Cookies and Web Beacons**

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, scripts and other similar technologies are used by Synacor and/or our advertising partners, affiliates, analytics and service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, advertising auditing and reporting, content personalization, administering the sites, tracking users’ movements around the site, and gathering demographic information about the user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We also use cookies to remember users’ settings (e.g. content preferences and, with user permission, passwords), and for authentication purposes. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

To manage Adobe Flash LSOs please click here:  
<https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

#### **Advertising**

We collaborate with third parties to display and manage advertising on the Synacor and Client Websites and mobile applications and to display and manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on those properties in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [https://www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [https://preferences-mgr.truste.com](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) [or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)]. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Sharing of Information by Synacor

We will not share your Personal Data with any individuals or non-affiliate companies except in the following circumstances:

**With Your Consent** : We will share your Personal Data outside of Synacor when we have your consent and only for the specific reasons for which you gave consent.

**Legal Reasons** : Synacor will share Personal Data if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary:

  * To comply with any applicable law, regulation or governmental request for information such as a subpoena, court order or similar legal process.
  * To enforce any applicable terms of use, terms of service or end user license agreement, including investigation of potential violations thereof.
  * To detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues.
  * To protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Synacor, its clients and their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

**External Processing** : Synacor provides Personal Data to its affiliates and other trusted businesses or persons to process the Personal Data for us, based on our written instructions and in compliance with law, and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. For example, we use service providers to help us with customer support.

**Business Transfers** : Synacor may transfer any information in our possession to any successor to all or substantially all of its business or assets that concern the Services. We will continue to ensure the confidentiality of your Personal Data.

**Aggregation** : Synacor may share with our partners (for example, with publishers and advertisers), aggregated usage and demographic information collected via the Synacor and Client Websites, third party web sites, mobile applications, and the Services. However, no Personal Data will be included in these aggregations. We also allow specific partners to collect information from your browser or device for advertising or measurement purposes using their own cookies or similar technologies.

**Affiliated Business We Do Not Control** : We are affiliated with a variety of businesses that jointly provide products or services with Synacor. When an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, we may share information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business that is necessary to provide the products and services. We only permit the use of any Personal Data by these affiliated businesses solely as necessary for such businesses to provide the requested products and services and for no other reason. This will be covered in a written agreement between Synacor and said third-party.

### Sharing Your Own Information with Others

If you choose to post comments to blogs, forums, or other editorial sections of the Synacor and Client Websites or mobile applications, any information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of such website. Therefore, when using blogs, forums, other editorial sections of the Synacor and Client Websites or mobile applications, or otherwise posting information online, we urge you to think carefully about including any Personal Data (name, address, passwords, medical information, or otherwise) that might be used to identify you or anyone else. When you publish this information, it becomes public and we are not responsible for what others may do with the information you choose to submit through these features.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone, you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

### Information Relating to Children

Neither the Synacor or Client Websites, mobile applications, nor the Services are designed for those 13 years of age and younger. Synacor does not knowingly collect Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13. If Synacor is made aware that it has received Personal Data from someone under 13, it will use reasonable efforts to remove that Personal Data from its records. Children under the age of 13 should not post in any of the blogs, forums, or other editorial sections of the Synacor or Client Websites or mobile applications.

### Updating/Accessing/Exporting/Amending/Correcting Personal Data

Synacor acknowledges that you have the right to access and export your Personal Data. If you are a user of the Client Websites or mobile applications, the information provided through those properties is owned and controlled by Synacor’s Clients. Please check the privacy policy on that particular Client Website or mobile applications for instructions on how to modify your Personal Data with the controller of that information. Synacor will respond within a reasonable amount of time not to exceed thirty (30) days, to a request by a data subject to remove personal data.

Synacor collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose Personal Data Synacor processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. If you are a user of Synacor’s Website and would like us to update, correct, delete, export or deactivate any Personal Data that you have provided to us on such website, please send your request to us at privacypolicy@synacor.com and we will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt, not to exceed thirty (30) days. Upon your request, Synacor will provide you with information about whether or not we hold any of your Personal Data.

### Data Retention

We will retain your information and the Personal Data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you Services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that, we no longer use your information to provide you Services contact us at [privacypolicy@synacor.com](mailto:privacypolicy@synacor.com). We will retain and use your information and Personal Data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### **Social Media (Features) and Widgets**

The Synacor and Client Websites and mobile applications may include social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button and widgets, such as the “Share This” button or interactive mini-programs that run on the Synacor and Client Websites and mobile applications. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Synacor and Client Websites or mobile applications. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the social media features. Any information that we collect from your social media account may depend on the privacy settings you have set with the social media site, so please consult the social media site’s privacy policy and data practices for further information.

### Security Procedures

Synacor has implemented a variety of security measures to protect Personal Data and other information received by Synacor, including containing all Personal Data behind its secured server network and limiting its accessibility to a limited number of authorized persons who have special access rights to such systems. Anyone with access to Personal Data is subject to strict confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Data submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. We also review our information collection, storage, and processing practices, including physical security measures, to prevent unauthorized access to our systems. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Additional Information

The Synacor and Client Websites and mobile applications may contain links to other sites. Synacor is not responsible for the privacy practices, the content or the products and services offered by such websites. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your Personal Data by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as Synacor. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you click on a link on the Synacor or Client Websites or in mobile applications and visit a third party website you should read that site’s privacy statement before providing any Personal Data.

### Framing

We utilize framing techniques on some pages of the Synacor and Client Websites to make it appear that the user is still on the Synacor or Client Websites when the user is actually on a third party website. Please be aware that if you are providing your Personal Data on these third party websites that you are providing such Personal Data to these third parties and not to Synacor and that the privacy policies of these third parties will apply to your Personal Data.

### Data Transfers

Your Personal Data may be processed on servers located outside of the country where you live. Data protection laws vary among countries, with some providing more protection than others provide. Regardless of where your information is processed, Synacor applies the same protections described in this Privacy Policy. We also comply with certain legal frameworks relating to the transfer of data, such as the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks as further described below.

When we receive formal written complaints, we respond by contacting the person who made the complaint. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of your Personal Data that we cannot resolve with you directly.

### Privacy Shield

Synacor and its subsidiary companies participate in and have certified their compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Synacor is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Privacy Shield Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>.

Synacor is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Synacor complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Synacor is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Synacor may be required to disclose personal data in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including but not limited to a request to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Upon certification with Privacy Shield, Synacor received a Certificate of Validation evidencing the company’s compliance with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework for Customer Data from an independent third party that specializes in compliance and security.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Synacor commits to resolve complaints about our collection, use, retention or transfer of your personal data. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Synacor at [privacypolicy@synacor.com](mailto:mailto:privacypolicy@synacor.com) (such inquiries or complaints shall hereinafter be referred to as “Privacy Shield Inquiries.”)

Synacor will provide an initial response to Privacy Shield Inquiries within thirty (30) days of receipt of the Inquiry. An extension may be granted under limited circumstances. Company has standard procedures for responding to Privacy Shield Inquiries. If there is any conflict between a data subject rights under the Privacy Shield Principles and the Company procedures for handling such inquiries, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.  
Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

Synacor has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred from the EU and Switzerland in the context of the employment relationship.

### Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We always indicate the date the last changes were published. If changes are significant, we will provide a prominent notice on the Synacor Websites and may provide email notification if warranted.

The last update to this Privacy Policy was on June 18, 2019.

Please direct all questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices and procedures outlined in this policy, and concerns regarding the Synacor Websites or Synacor’s Mobile App to the following:

Synacor, Inc.  
Privacy Policy Administrator  
40 La Riviere Drive, Suite 300  
Buffalo, NY 14202  

In addition to the policies above, the following items refer specifically to [www.synacor.com](https://www.synacor.com/).

We collect Personal Data on www.synacor.com when you apply for a job. If you apply for a job, we collect through our job application service provider, information including your name (first and last), email, physical address, phone number and resume. We use a third party service provider to manage our job postings and resume submittals. The third party is prohibited from using your Personal Data for promotional purposes.

We post customer testimonials, comments and reviews on the company websites that may contain Personal Data. We do obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you want your testimonial, comments or reviews removed please contact us at [privacypolicy@synacor.com](mailto:privacypolicy@synacor.com).

You will not receive any communications from the Synacor.com website unless you contact us for a specific request or submit a job application. See above how to modify your Personal Data submitted.

In addition to the policies above, the following items refer specifically to [www.zimbra.com](https://www.zimbra.com/)

We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities such as processing payments. These companies have authorization to use your Personal Data only as necessary to provide these Services to Company.
